In this video I'm going to demonstrate how
as a professor you're going to use
LecturePilot and sign in and going to create
courses and also afterwards
how this created courses then shown to
students and how students can interact
with it. So as a user of LecturePilot you're
signing in using your Alma
credentials.
Then as a professor you're going to enter
the course name you want to create.
Your input is matched against ILIAS and Alma
courses and here it found the Alma
course I want to create.
I'm now going to upload all the materials I
have for this course, all my teaching
materials.
They don't have to be filtered as we can see
here.
unsupported materials are just ignored.
You don't have to put all into PDF formats
or something.
Just upload your materials as you have them.
That's totally fine. Everything is taken
care of.
Now it from the materials it loaded how many
lectures and in each
lecture with its dedicated title and when
this lecture is going to take place.
All this got extracted from the uploaded
materials.
I'm gonna apply the schedule.
In this step, it's now taking the uploaded
materials and for the just extracted
lectures, for the 14 lectures we've seen, it
now on a per lecture level decides
what of the uploaded files are relevant to
what lecture and assigns them to the
specific lecture.
Okay, it's now done assigning the files to
specific lectures.
If you're going to click on show details,
you can have a look at exactly what
files it used, what are ignored completely,
and on a file or, yeah, on a
per file level, we can see what file is used
for what lecture.
for example lecture one is obviously used
only for lecture one but we can also
say this is like a document that's course
wide relevant for example.
We now have the chance to select YouTube
videos with which we want to enrich
the canvas
So now it's going to propose like a learning
schedule, a
learning plan and learning goals for each
lecture.
We can see this here with lecture one
already.
So for lecture one, it has defined three
different learning goals.
We can have a look at the goal defined.
We can see where it got this goal from or
extracted it from our materials.
And if this doesn't align with our
intention, our actual lecture,
we can here edit the goals and update and
change them.
I'm going to now approve the learning goals
for all the lectures.
And now it's for all these lectures with the
approved learning goals,
it's generating the learning canvases.
So basically the interface or learning
canvas the student
is later interacting with is now generated
and per lecture.
Okay, so all the lecture canvases have no
been generated and we can open them and
add them and have a look at them.
So this is how this lecture will be
presented or looking for the students
if they log in into LecturePilot.
We can see here the extracted slides, all
the additional content generated.
This looks good.
So we are going to review and approve all
these separate lectures.
We again here have now the overview about
the generated canvas and can preview
this one or like the generated canvas and
can also again have a look at the
review or like learning outcomes that have
been defined.
I'm going to approve all the separate
lectures.
Now that we approved all them, we can
publish this whole workspace, all the
different lectures.
And they have been published now, so if you
go to manage courses,
we can see here the Grundlagen des
maschinellen Lernens course, we see all the
lectures, we see when this lecture becomes
public.
We can change the settings, like the access
settings for a specific lecture.
And we can, of course, can preview as a
student.
What I'm going to do now is I'm going to log
out as a professor.
I'm going to look in as a student and we
already see here, okay,
I am signed up to the Grundlagen des
maschinellen Lernens course.
I see all the lectures here. I can set as a
student for a lecture, whether I was
absent or present. Based on this selection,
the AI tutor will adapt and rather
check all the concepts with me if I was
present, whether I understood them, if I
was absent, lead me or more guide me through
the materials and ensure
my understanding.
I can do exam checks. These are quizzes
across all the lectures
basically with which I can get fast or quick
feedback in about
my understanding and a knowledge level.
let us actually go into a, um, lecture.
Let's go into a lecture four, maybe.
I'm now as in the student view. So I have
the tutor here on the right hand side.
We can see now I have open-ended question
checkpoints and also,
okay, in this lecture, we don't have a quiz.
So I'm gonna answer here anything like no
clue.
My answer is then given to the agent.
And it has as a context that I am answered
onto like a quiz or checkpoint.
And the agent now scrolls within like the
learning canvas to the section that's
relevant to the question I missed or like
answered wrong.
Because this section is relevant to that
question.
And so it understood what my question got
wrong and led me to the concept that's
relevant.
For example, I can ask it,
explain non-linear regression.
So here I see non-linear regression is like
someone relevant
and I ask it to explain this unto me.
it again scrolled to the section that's
relevant to this, provided we have an
answer.
But I could also ask it to explain this to
me with a
dog and cat example.
So, again, scroll to the section that's
relevant.
I now explicitly asked it to create a new
section to show this feature.
Okay, what it did now, it created a new
section because I asked it to create a
new section with like a dog and cat example,
right?
Obviously there is no dog and cat example in
the materials uploaded
by you, the professor, right? So it now
created a
section custom to like the student's
preference or like
example kinda and explains this
nonlinear concept now with dog and cat
example.
I can also generate practice exams, select
the amount of questions
I want to as a student and the duration
which also adjusts like the complexity of
the questions kind of.
I'm going to generate an exam now
Okay, so the exam has generated now and we
can see we can take this exam directly
in the browser. I can select the options
here.
But I actually prefer doing exams like
handwritten.
So what I can do, I'm going to download the
exam PDF.
And I'm going to download the solutions PDF.
That's the generated exam.
So here we again see it supports open-ended
question.
It supports multiple choice. It's a whole
exam.
we have the solutions right here.
these are the solutions. For all the
questions one, two, three here again we see
the solutions so we can yeah grade basically
our selves.
Also, if I go into a lecture, here I have
the tutor on the side, right?
And as a student, I can ask them, like, what
is this lecture about?
So it now shows or answered us. The session
goal is by the end of the lecture,
you should be able to explain how model
complexity affects generalization,
evaluate models honestly. So these basically
are like the learning objectives,
right? The learning outcomes, the learning
goals we have defined during the
course creation.
These are now the goals or objective the
tutor uses and tests the student
against, right?